Guide to the Yale Classes Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Pictures of Yale Classes, 1806-1971; Series I
  - Class of 1894
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 34, Folder 365)
  - Class of 1894 -- Law: Class pictures (Box 34, Folder 366)
  - Class of 1894s
    - Class pictures (Box 34, Folder 367)
    - Class pictures (Box 34, Folder 368)
    - 15th Reunion, 1908 (Box 34, Folder 368)
    - 20th Reunion, 1914 (Box 34, Folder 369)
    - Reunion, 1937 (Box 34, Folder 369)
    - 45th Reunion, 1938 (Box 34, Folder 369)
    - Reunion, 1940 (Box 34, Folder 370)
    - 50th Reunion, 1944 (Box 34, Folder 370)
    - Victory Reunion (Box 34, Folder 370)
  - Class of 1895
    - Class pictures (Box 35, Folder 371)
    - Small groups (Box 35, Folder 372)
    - Mounted snapshots (Box 35, Folder 372)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1901 (Box 35, Folder 373)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1905 (Box 35, Folder 373)
    - 15th Reunion, 1910 (Box 35, Folder 373)
    - Planting Class tree, 1915 (Box 35, Folder 374)
    - 20th Reunion, 1915 (Box 35, Folder 374)
    - 25th Reunion, 1920 (Box 35, Folder 375)
    - 30th Reunion, 1925 (Box 35, Folder 376)
    - 35th Reunion, 1930 (Box 35, Folder 376)
    - 40th Reunion, 1935 (Box 35, Folder 376)
    - 45th Reunion, 1939 (Box 35, Folder 377)
    - 50th Reunion, 1943 (Box 35, Folder 377)
    - 55th Reunion, 1948 (Box 35, Folder 377)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 35, Folder 378)
  - Class of 1895 -- Law: Class pictures (Box 35, Folder 379)
  - Class of 1895s
    - Class pictures (Box 35, Folder 380)
    - Reunion, 1908 (Box 35, Folder 381)
    - 20th Reunion, 1915 (Box 35, Folder 381)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 35, Folder 381)
  - Class of 1896
    - Class pictures (Box 36, Folder 382)
    - Students on fence (Box 36, Folder 382)
    - Class Day (Box 36, Folder 382)
    - Small group (Box 36, Folder 383)
    - Assorted snapshot (Box 36, Folder 384)
    - Triennial Reunion (tintype), 1899 (Box 36, Folder 385)
    - 5th Reunion (band), 1901 (Box 36, Folder 385)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1902 (Box 36, Folder 385)
    - Deccennial Reunion, 1906 (Box 36, Folder 386)
    - Quindecennial Reunion, 1911 (Box 36, Folder 386)
    - 20th Reunion, 1916 (Box 36, Folder 387)
    - 25th Reunion, 1921 (Box 36, Folder 387)
    - 35th Reunion, 1941 (Box 36, Folder 387)
    - 40th Reunion, 1946 (Box 36, Folder 388)
    - Reunion, 1938 (Box 36, Folder 388)
    - 45th Reunion, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 389)
    - Reunion, 1942 (Box 36, Folder 389)
    - 50th Reunion, 1956 (Box 36, Folder 389)
    - 55th Reunion, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 389)
    - 50th Reunion, 1956 (Box 37, Folder 390)
    - 55th Reunion, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 390)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 37, Folder 390)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 37, Folder 391)
    - Long Distance Cup (Box 37, Folder 391)
    - Class Banners (Box 37, Folder 391)
    - Reunion of Phillips Andover with class of 1896 men (Box 37, Folder 392)
    - Ambulance donated to England in 1941 (Box 37, Folder 393)
  - Class of 1896 Medical: class pictures (Box 37, Folder 394)
  - Class of 1896s
    - Class pictures (Box 37, Folder 394)
    - Small groups (Box 37, Folder 396-397)
    - Individual portrait (Box 37, Folder 398)
    - Individual portraits (Box 38, Folder 399-401)
    - Vicennial Reunion, 1916 (Box 38, Folder 402)
    - 25th Reunion, 1921 (Box 38, Folder 402)
    - 45th Reunion, 1941 (Box 38, Folder 402)
    - 55th Reunion, 1951 (Box 38, Folder 403)
    - 65th Reunion, 1961 (Box 38, Folder 403)
  - Class of 1897
    - Class pictures (Box 38, Folder 404)
    - Students on fence (Box 38, Folder 404)
    - Small groups (Box 38, Folder 405)
    - WWI Ambulance (donated) (Box 38, Folder 405)
    - Portrait of C.U. Clark (Box 38, Folder 405)
    - Yale student groups--taken by Francis P. Garvan (Box 38, Folder 406)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1900 (Box 38, Folder 407)
    - Reunion, [1908?] (Box 38, Folder 407)
    - 35th Reunion, 1932 (Box 38, Folder 407)
    - 40th Reunion, 1937 (Box 38, Folder 408)
    - Reunion, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 409)
    - Reunion, 1941 (Box 38, Folder 409)
    - 45th Reunion(s), 1942 (Box 38, Folder 409)
    - Reunion, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 410)
    - Reunion, 1944 (Box 39, Folder 410)
    - 50th Reunion, 1947 (Box 39, Folder 411)
    - 55th Reunion, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 411)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 39, Folder 411)
  - Class of 1897 -- Law Reunion, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 412)
  - Class of 1897 -- Medical
    - Class pictures, 1897 (Box 39, Folder 412A)
    - [Reunion], Undated (Box 39, Folder 413)
  - Class of 1897s: Class picture
    - Small group (Box 39, Folder 414)
    - 10th Reunion, 1907 (Box 39, Folder 415)
    - 45th Reunion, 1942 (Box 39, Folder 415)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 39, Folder 415)
  - Class of 1898
    - Students on fence (Box 39, Folder 416)
    - Class Day (Box 39, Folder 416)
    - Graduation (Box 39, Folder 416)
    - Class photo taken in front of Osborne Hall (Box 39, Folder 416)
    - Triennial Reunion (Box 39, Folder 417)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1904 (Box 39, Folder 417)
    - 10th Reunion, 1908 (Box 39, Folder 418)
    - 15th Reunion, 1913 (Box 39, Folder 418)
    - 20th Reunion, 1918 (Box 39, Folder 419)
    - Dinner, 1922 (Box 39, Folder 419)
    - 25th Reunion, 1923 (Box 39, Folder 419)
    - 40th Reunion, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 420)
    - 45th Reunion, 1943 (Box 39, Folder 420)
    - 55th Reunion, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 420)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 39, Folder 421)
  - Class of 1898s
    - Class picture (Box 39, Folder 421)
    - Small groups (Box 39, Folder 422)
    - Small groups (Box 39, Folder 423)
    - Orchestra(?) (Box 39, Folder 423)
    - Individual Portrait (Box 39, Folder 424-425)
    - Individual portrait (Box 40, Folder 426-428)
    - 10th Reunion, 1908 (Box 40, Folder 429)
    - 60th(?) Reunion, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 429)
  - Class of 1899
    - Class picture (Box 40, Folder 430)
    - Small group (Box 40, Folder 430)
    - Assorted Snapshot (Box 40, Folder 431)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1902 (Box 40, Folder 432)
    - 15th Reunion, 1914 (Box 40, Folder 432)
    - 20th Reunion, 1919 (Box 40, Folder 432)
    - 25th Reunion, 1924 (Box 40, Folder 433)
    - 30th Reunion, 1929 (Box 40, Folder 433)
    - 35th Reunion, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 433)
    - 40th Reunion, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 434)
    - 45th Reunion, 1943 (Box 40, Folder 434)
    - 50th Reunion, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 435)
    - 55th Reunion, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 435)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 40, Folder 435)
  - Class of 1899 --Law: Class picture (Box 40, Folder 436)
  - Class of 1899s
    - Class Day (Box 40, Folder 436)
    - Small group (Box 40, Folder 437)
    - 10th Reunion, 1908 (Box 40, Folder 438)
    - 35th Reunion, 1934 (Box 40, Folder 438)
    - 40th Reunion, 1939 (Box 40, Folder 438)
  - Class of 1900
    - Class picture (Box 41, Folder 439)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1903 (Box 41, Folder 439)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1906 (Box 41, Folder 439)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 440)
    - 40th Reunion, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 441)
    - 45th Reunion, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 441)
    - 55th Reunion, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 441)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 41, Folder 441)
  - Class of 1900s
    - Class Day (Box 41, Folder 441)
    - Biography group (Box 41, Folder 442)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1903 (Box 41, Folder 442)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1910 (Box 41, Folder 443)
    - Quindecennial Reunion, 1915 (Box 41, Folder 443)
    - Vicennial Reunion, 1920 (Box 41, Folder 443)
    - 25th Reunion, 1925 (Box 41, Folder 444)
    - 35th Reunion, 1935 (Box 41, Folder 444)
    - 40th Reunion, 1940 (Box 41, Folder 444)
    - 45th (?) Reunion, 1945 (Box 41, Folder 445)
    - 50th Reunion, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 445)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 41, Folder 445)
  - Class of 1901
    - Class picture (Box 41, Folder 446)
    - Small group (Box 41, Folder 446)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1911 (Box 41, Folder 446)
    - Quindecennial Reunion, 1916 (Box 41, Folder 447)
    - Vicennial Reunion, 1921
    - 40th Reunion, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 448)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 41, Folder 448)
  - Class of 1901s
    - Class picture, 1901 (Box 41, Folder 448)
    - Small groups (Box 41, Folder 449)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1911 (Box 41, Folder 449)
    - Quindecennial Reunion, 1916 (Box 41, Folder 450)
    - 25th Reunion, 1926 (Box 41, Folder 450)
    - 40th Reunion, 1941 (Box 41, Folder 451)
    - 45th Reunion, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 451)
    - Dinner, 1949 (Box 41, Folder 451)
    - 50th Reunion, 1951 (Box 41, Folder 452)
    - Reunion, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 452)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 41, Folder 452)
  - Class of 1902
    - Individual portraits (Box 42, Folder 453-455)
    - Newspaper photo (Box 42, Folder 456)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1908 (Box 42, Folder 456)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1912 (Box 42, Folder 456)
    - Quindecennial Reunion, 1917 (Box 42, Folder 457)
    - 25th Reunion, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 457)
    - Reunion, 1938 (Box 42, Folder 457)
    - Reunion, 1939 (Box 42, Folder 458)
    - Reunion, 1940 (Box 42, Folder 458)
    - 40th Reunion, 1942 (Box 42, Folder 458)
    - 65th Reunion, 1967 (Box 42, Folder 459)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 42, Folder 459)
  - Class of 1902s
    - Class picture (Box 42, Folder 460)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1908 (Box 42, Folder 460)
    - 25th Reunion, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 461)
    - 30th (?) Reunion, 1932 (Box 42, Folder 461)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 42, Folder 461)
  - Class of 1903
    - Class picture, 1903 (Box 42, Folder 462)
    - Small group (Box 42, Folder 462)
    - Individual portraits (Box 42, Folder 462)
    - Snapshots (Box 42, Folder 463)
    - 1903 cup (Box 42, Folder 463)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1906 (Box 42, Folder 463)
    - 5th Reunion, 1908 (Box 42, Folder 464)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1909 (Box 42, Folder 464)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1913 (Box 42, Folder 464)
    - Decennial Gift to Yale Library, 1913 (Box 42, Folder 465)
    - 25th Reunion, 1928 (Box 42, Folder 465)
    - 55th Reunion, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 465)
    - Various Reunions--includes one tintype (Box 43, Folder 466)
    - Reunion (cruise on S.S. Bergensford), Undated (Box 43, Folder 466)
  - Class of 1903 -- Forestry: Class picture (Box 43, Folder 467)
  - Class of 1903 -- Medical: Small groups (Box 43, Folder 468)
  - Class of 1903s
    - Small group (Box 43, Folder 468)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1909 (Box 43, Folder 469)
    - 25th Reunion, 1928 (Box 43, Folder 469)
    - 55th Reunion, 1958 (Box 43, Folder 470)
    - 65th Reunion, 1968 (Box 43, Folder 470)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 43, Folder 470)
  - Class of 1904
    - Triennial Reunion, 1907 (Box 43, Folder 471)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1910 (Box 43, Folder 471)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 471)
    - Quindecennial Reunion, 1919 (Box 43, Folder 472)
    - Vicennial Reunion, 1924 (Box 43, Folder 472)
    - 45th Reunion, 1949 (Box 43, Folder 472)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 43, Folder 472)
  - Class of 1904 & 1904s: 25th Reunion, 1929 (Box 43, Folder 473)
  - Class of 1904s
    - Small group (Box 43, Folder 473)
    - 35th Reunion, 1939 (Box 43, Folder 474)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 43, Folder 474)
  - Class of 1905
    - Senior groups (Box 43, Folder 475)
    - Individual portraits (Box 43, Folder 475)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1907 (Box 43, Folder 475)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1910 (Box 43, Folder 476)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1914 (Box 43, Folder 476)
    - 15th Reunion, 1920 (Box 43, Folder 476)
    - 20th Reunion, 1925 (Box 43, Folder 477)
    - 25th Reunion, 1929 (Box 43, Folder 477)
    - Reunion, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 477)
    - 35th Reunion, 1940 (Box 43, Folder 478)
    - 45th Reunion, 1950 (Box 43, Folder 478)
    - 55th Reunion, 1955 (Box 43, Folder 478)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 43, Folder 478)
  - Class of 1905s
    - Triennial Reunion, 1908 (Box 43, Folder 478)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1911 (Box 43, Folder 479)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1915 (Box 43, Folder 480)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 43, Folder 480)
  - Class of 1906
    - Decennial Preparedness Encampment, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 481)
    - Reunion, 1926 or 1931 (Box 43, Folder 481)
    - 35th Reunion, 1941 (Box 43, Folder 481)
    - 65th Reunion, 1971 (Box 43, Folder 482)
    - Reunions (?), Undated (Box 43, Folder 482)
  - Class of 1906s
    - Small groups (Box 43, Folder 482)
    - Biennial Reunion, 1908 (Box 43, Folder 483)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1912 (Box 43, Folder 483)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1916 (Box 43, Folder 484)
    - Victory Reunion (Box 43, Folder 484)
    - Quindecennial Reunion, 1921 (Box 43, Folder 484)
  - Class of 1907
    - 30th Reunion, 1937 (Box 43, Folder 485)
    - 35th Reunion, 1942 (Box 43, Folder 485)
    - 50th Reunion, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 485)
    - 60th Reunion, 1967 (Box 43, Folder 485)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 43, Folder 485)
  - Class of 1907s
    - Small group (Box 43, Folder 485)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1910 (Box 44, Folder 486)
    - 35th Reunion, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 486)
    - 60th Reunion, 1967 (Box 44, Folder 487)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 44, Folder 487)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 44, Folder 488)
    - Reunion picture keys (Box 44, Folder 488)
  - Class of 1908
    - Students on fence (Box 44, Folder 489)
    - Snapshots, 1905-1906 (Box 44, Folder 489)
    - Class Day (Box 44, Folder 489)
    - 8th Reunion, 1916 (Box 44, Folder 490)
    - 15th Reunion, 1923 (Box 44, Folder 490)
    - 30th Reunion, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 490)
    - 45th Reunion, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 491)
    - 50th Reunion, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 491)
    - Laying Corner stone--Tate Foster House, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 491)
    - 60th Reunion, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 492)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 44, Folder 492)
    - Assorted later snapshots (Box 44, Folder 492)
  - Classes 1908 & 1908s: 60th Reunion, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 493)
  - Class of 1908, Yale Law School (Box 44, Folder 493A)
  - Class of 1908s
    - Class pictures (Box 44, Folder 493)
    - Senior group (Box 44, Folder 494)
    - Individual portraits (Box 44, Folder 495-501)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1911 (Box 44, Folder 501)
    - Decennial War Reunion, 1918 (Box 44, Folder 502)
    - 30th Reunion, 1938 (Box 44, Folder 502)
    - 45th Reunion, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 502)
    - Gift to Starr Barnum, 1958 (Box 44, Folder 503)
    - 60th Reunion, 1968 (Box 44, Folder 503)
  - Class of 1909
    - Individual portrait (Box 45, Folder 504)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1912 (Box 45, Folder 504)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1915 (Box 45, Folder 505)
    - 10th Reunion?, 1919 (Box 45, Folder 505)
    - Quindecennial Reunion, 1924 (Box 45, Folder 506)
    - 40th Reunion, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 506)
    - 60th Reunion, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 506)
  - Class of 1909s
    - Small group (Box 45, Folder 506)
    - Individual portrait (Box 45, Folder 507)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1912 (Box 45, Folder 507)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1919 (Box 45, Folder 508)
    - Quindecennial Reunion, 1924 (Box 45, Folder 508)
    - 25th Reunion, 1934 (Box 45, Folder 509)
    - 60th Reunion, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 509)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 45, Folder 509)
  - Class of 1910
    - Class pictures (Box 45, Folder 510)
    - Small groups (Box 45, Folder 510)
    - Class Day (Box 45, Folder 511)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1913 (Box 45, Folder 511)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1916 (Box 45, Folder 511)
    - Quindeciennal Reunion, 1925 (Box 45, Folder 512)
    - 40th Reunion, 1950 (Box 45, Folder 512)
    - 50th Reunion, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 513)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 45, Folder 513)
  - Class of 1910s
    - Small groups (Box 45, Folder 513)
    - Triennial Reunion, 1913 (Box 45, Folder 514)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1916 (Box 45, Folder 514)
    - Victory Reunion, 1919 (Box 45, Folder 514)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1920 (Box 45, Folder 515)
    - 30th Reunion, 1940 (Box 45, Folder 516)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 45, Folder 516)
  - Class of 1911
    - Class Supper (Box 45, Folder 517)
    - Senior Class Prom (Box 45, Folder 517)
    - Commencement (Box 45, Folder 517)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1921 (Box 45, Folder 518)
    - Field Day, 1925 (Box 45, Folder 518)
    - 25th Reunion, 1936 (Box 45, Folder 518)
    - Informal Reunion, 1937 (Box 46, Folder 519)
    - 30th Reunion, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 519)
    - 30th or 35th Reunion, 1941-1946 (Box 46, Folder 519)
    - 40th Reunion, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 520-521)
    - 45th Reunion, 1956 (Box 46, Folder 521)
    - 50th Reunion, 1961 (Box 46, Folder 521)
    - 60th Reunion, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 522)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 46, Folder 522)
    - Assorted later snapshots (Box 46, Folder 523)
    - 25 later individual portraits (Box 46, Folder 523)
    - Pictorial Response to 1952 Questionnaire: (Box 46, Folder 523)
    - Later snapshots (Box 46, Folder 524)
    - 9 later individual portraits (Box 46, Folder 524)
  - Class of 1911s
    - Small groups (Box 46, Folder 525)
    - Reunion, 1939 (Box 46, Folder 526)
    - 30th Reunion, 1941 (Box 46, Folder 526)
    - 40th Reunion, 1951 (Box 46, Folder 526)
  - Class of 1912
    - Class pictures (Box 46, Folder 527)
    - Assorted snapshots (including one tintype) (Box 46, Folder 527)
    - 1st Reunion, 1913 (Box 47, Folder 528)
    - 30th Reunion, 1942 (Box 47, Folder 528)
    - 35th Reunion, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 529-531)
    - 40th Reunion, 1952 (Box 47, Folder 532)
    - 45th Reunion, 1957 (Box 48, Folder 533-535)
    - 50th Reunion, 1962 (Box 48, Folder 536-537)
    - 55th Reunion, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 537)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 48, Folder 537)
  - Classes of 1912 and 1912s, 55th reunion, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 538)
  - Class of 1912s
    - Small groups (Box 48, Folder 538)
    - Decennial Reunion, 1922 1922 (Box 48, Folder 539)
    - 55th Reunion, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 539)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 48, Folder 539)
  - Class of 1913
    - Assorted snapshots (Box 48, Folder 540)
    - 15th Reunion, 1928 (Box 48, Folder 540)
    - 25th Reunion, 1938 (Box 48, Folder 540)
    - 45th Reunion, 1958 (Box 48, Folder 541)
    - 55th Reunion, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 541)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 48, Folder 541)
  - Class of 1913s
    - Small groups (Box 48, Folder 541)
    - 55th Reunion, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 542)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 49, Folder 542)
  - Class of 1914
    - 25th Reunion, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 543)
    - 35th Reunion, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 543)
    - 40th Reunion, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 543)
    - 45th Reunion, 1959 (Box 49, Folder 544)
    - 50th Reunion, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 544)
    - 55th Reunion, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 544)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 49, Folder 545)
  - Class of 1914s
    - Small group (Box 49, Folder 545)
    - Individual portrait (Box 49, Folder 546)
    - 35th Reunion, 1949 (Box 49, Folder 546)
    - 55th Reunion, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 546)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 49, Folder 547)
  - Class of 1915
    - Assorted snapshots (Box 49, Folder 548)
    - Class portrait in front of Osborn Hall, Circa 1915 (Box 49, Folder 548)
  - Class of 1915s
    - Small group (Box 49, Folder 549)
    - Reunion, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 549)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 49, Folder 549)
  - Class of 1916
    - Assorted snapshots (Box 49, Folder 550)
    - Triennial reunion, 1919 (Box 49, Folder 550)
    - 25th reunion, 1941 June 16 (Box 49, Folder 550)
    - 30th reunion, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 550)
    - 55th reunion, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 550)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 49, Folder 550)
    - High School group of Class member (Box 49, Folder 551)
  - Class of 1916s
    - Small groups (Box 49, Folder 551)
    - 30th Reunion, 1946 (Box 49, Folder 552)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 49, Folder 552)
  - Class of 1917
    - Assorted snapshot (Box 49, Folder 553)
    - 15th(?) Reunion, 1932 (Box 49, Folder 553)
    - 20th Reunion, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 553)
    - Father & Son Dinner, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 553)
    - 50th Reunion, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 554)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 49, Folder 554-555)
  - Class of 1917 & 1917s: 50th Reunion, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 556)
  - Class of 1917 Divinity: Class picture (Box 49, Folder 557)
  - Class of 1917s
    - Small group (Box 49, Folder 557)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 49, Folder 558)
  - Class of 1918
    - 40th(?) Reunion, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 559)
    - 50th Reunion, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 559)
  - Class of 1918s
    - Small group (Box 50, Folder 560)
    - Dinner, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 560)
    - 40th Reunion, 1958 (Box 50, Folder 561)
    - 50th Reunion, 1968 (Box 50, Folder 561)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 50, Folder 561)
  - Class of 1919
    - Freshman Banquet (Box 50, Folder 562)
    - Father & Son Dinner, 1941 (Box 50, Folder 562)
    - 35th Reunion, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 562)
    - 40th Reunion, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 563)
    - 45th Reunion, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 563)
    - 50th Reunion, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 563)
    - Small group (Box 50, Folder 564)
    - 30th Reunion, 1949 (Box 50, Folder 564)
    - 50th Reunion, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 564)
  - Class of 1919s
    - Triennial, 1919 (Box 56)
    - 15th Reunion, 1934 (Box 56)
    - 20th Reunion, 1939 (Box 56)
    - 26th Reunion, 1945 (Box 56)
    - 30th Reunion, 1949 (Box 56)
    - 1961 (Box 56)
  - Class of 1920
    - Class picture (Box 50, Folder 565)
    - 45th Reunion, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 565)
    - 50th Reunion, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 565)
    - 60th Reunion (Box 50, Folder 566)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 50, Folder 566)
  - Class of 1920s
    - Class Day (Box 50, Folder 566)
    - Graduation (Box 50, Folder 567)
    - Small group (Box 50, Folder 567)
    - 1st Reunion, 1921 (Box 50, Folder 567)
    - Sexennial Reunion, 1926 (Box 50, Folder 568)
    - 10th Reunion, 1930 (Box 50, Folder 568)
    - 15th Reunion, 1935 (Box 50, Folder 568)
    - 20th Reunion, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 569)
    - 30th Reunion, 1950 (Box 50, Folder 570)
    - 35th Reunion, 1955 (Box 50, Folder 570)
    - 40th Reunion, 1960 (Box 50, Folder 570)
    - 45th Reunion, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 570)
    - 50th Reunion, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 571)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 50, Folder 571)
    - Dance (Box 50, Folder 571)
    - Theta Xi House Parties, 1918-1920 (Box 51, Folder 572)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 572)
  - Class of 1921
    - 30th Reunion, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 573)
    - 50th Reunion, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 573)
    - Reunions, Undated (Box 51, Folder 573)
  - Class of 1921s
    - Small group (Box 51, Folder 573)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 574)
  - Class of 1922
    - Class Boy (Box 51, Folder 575)
    - 15th Reunion, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 575)
    - 20th Reunion, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 575)
    - 40th Reunion, 1962 (Box 51, Folder 575A)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 575)
  - Class of 1922s: Small group (Box 51, Folder 576)
  - Classes of 1922 & 1922s 45th Reunion, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 577)
  - Class of 1923
    - 45th Reunion, 1968 (Box 51, Folder 578)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 578)
  - Class of 1923 Law Reunion, 1941 (Box 51, Folder 579)
  - Class of 1923s: Small groups (Box 51, Folder 580)
  - Class of 1924: 45th Reunion, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 581)
  - Classes of 1924 & 1924s 15th Reunion, 1939 (Box 51, Folder 582)
  - Class of 1924s
    - Small group (Box 51, Folder 582)
    - Dinner, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 583)
    - 15th Reunion, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 583)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 584)
  - Class of 1925
    - 15th Reunion, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 585)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 585)
  - Class of 1925 -- Medical, Undated (Box 51, Folder 585A)
  - Class of 1925s: Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 586)
  - Class of 1926
    - Snapshot (Box 51, Folder 587)
    - 25th Reunion, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 587)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 587)
  - Classes of 1926 & 1926s 45th Reunion, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 588)
  - Class of 1927
    - 10th Reunion, 1937 (Box 51, Folder 589)
    - 25th Reunion, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 589)
    - 40th Reunion, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 589)
    - Reunion, Undated (Box 51, Folder 590)